<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <origin/>
                <pubdate>20240416</pubdate>
                <title>Equity Index 2024</title>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>The Equity Index is an interactive tool visually highlighting disparities in Tacoma. The 2024 iteration uses 29 data points sorted into 5 determinant categories (Accessibility, Livability, Education, Economy, and Environmental Health) to determine where community members cannot access services or where services do not meet community needs. It is one of the primary tools that City staff, partners, and other decision-makers use to help ensure they make data-informed decisions to improve access to opportunities for all community members.Tacoma's original 2018 Equity Index was generated by The Kirwan Institute for the Study of Race &amp;amp; Ethnicity for Tacoma's Office of Equity and Human Rights.  Please note that the 2018 &amp;amp; 2020 versions of the Equity Index are based on 2010 US Census block groups. The 2022 and 2024 versions are based on 2020 US Census block groups. Census block groups have been clipped to the Puget Sound shoreline. Please read the complete metadata: Tacoma Equity Index 2024 Metadata.To learn more about the Equity Index, visit: CityofTacoma.org/EquityIndex.For questions, please fill out the Equity Index Inquiries form. Recommended symbology:
  
  Equity Index (Opportunity) field value
  
  
  HEX Code 50% transparency
  
 
 
  
  Very High
  
  
  #7F0000 
  
 
 
  
  High
  
  
  #D7301F
  
 
 
  
  Moderate
  
  
  #FC8D59
  
 
 
  
  Low
  
  
  #FDD49E
  
 
 
  
  Very Low
  
  
  #FAFCCF
  
 
</abstract>
            <purpose>The Equity Index is an interactive mapping tool showing how access to opportunity is distributed in Tacoma to help facilitate data-driven decision-making processes. The Equity Index is evaluated and updated every 2 years. This current iteration is for 2024. This feature layer is intended for analysis purposes.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <status>
            <update>None planned</update>
        </status>
        <spdom>
            <bounding>
                <westbc>-122.56199999998968</westbc>
                <eastbc>-122.34899999998969</eastbc>
                <northbc>47.31899999999601</northbc>
                <southbc>47.16699999999601</southbc>
            </bounding>
        </spdom>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>equity</themekey>
            </theme>
            <theme>
                <themekt>ISO 19115 Topic Categories</themekt>
                <themekey>society</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>Disclaimer | City of Tacoma Open Data</useconst>
        <datacred>City of Tacoma, Office of Strategy</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <cntorgp>
                    <cntorg>City of Tacoma</cntorg>
                </cntorgp>
                <cntaddr>
                    <addrtype>physical</addrtype>
                    <city>Tacoma</city>
                    <state>Washington</state>
                    <postal>98405</postal>
                </cntaddr>
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
